o2wifi.co.uk 2015-10-30

# O2 Wifi

These terms, our Fair Usage Policy and our Privacy Policy together make up the terms and conditions (the "Terms") for Telefónica UK Limited's O2 Wifi wireless communication service (the "Service"). Please read them carefully, so that you fully understand the Service that you are signing up to and plan to use. The Terms explain what you can use the Service for and the ways in which we will provide the Service and how we will use data that we collect as part of your use of the Service.

If anything's unclear, contact us at [admin@o2wifi.co.uk](mailto:admin@o2wifi.co.uk "Email admin@o2wifi.co.uk") or before accepting the Terms or using the Service.

If you're already an O2 customer then these Terms are in addition to the terms of the other services that you already take from O2.

 **O2**  
Telefónica UK Limited, 260 Bath Road, Slough, Berkshire SL1 4DX  
Registered in England and Wales No.1743099. Registered Office as above.  
© Telefónica UK Limited 2015.

The following Policy relates to your use of our O2 Wifi Service only. It is designed to make sure we can give you a Service that is great value, fast and reliable.

You must make sure that any use of the Service, by yourself or anyone else via your account, complies with this Policy. If you (or anyone else using the Service via your account) breach this Policy, we may:

This Policy is in addition to the Terms and Conditions for O2 Wifi and is part of the Terms for that Service. Anything which is not defined in this Policy will have the meaning set out in the Terms. If there's any inconsistency between the Policy and the Terms, the Policy will prevail.

 **O2**  
Telefónica UK Limited, 260 Bath Road, Slough, Berkshire SL1 4DX  
Registered in England and Wales No.1743099. Registered Office as above.  
© Telefónica UK Limited 2015. (July 2015)

## Our Privacy Policy

This privacy policy explains what personal information we have, how we use it and how you can check and update any personal information we have about you.

Watch our video below to learn more about our Privacy Policy.

### Why do we have your personal information?

We collect information to help us manage your account:

  * To deliver products and services to you (whether we provide them or not)
  * To improve our products and services and develop new ones
  * And to manage our network and help us run and grow our business

We also collect information so we can tell you about our products and services or allow partners we've chosen to tell you directly about their products. The law requires us to keep some information, too.

Sometimes we create and anonymise information so you can't be identified.

To find out more, click on any of the sections below.

  * The type of Information we have
  * Where do we get your information?
  * How we use your information
  * How we share your information
  * We keep hold of your information
  * Want to check and update your information?
  * Important things to know

Back to the top

### The type of Information we have

Without some of your information, we couldn't do our job (or get better at it.) This includes things like who you are, where you are, and how you're going to pay for your services.

**Who you are, which includes:**

  * Your name, address, gender, age, interests and such.  
You can find these in your MyO2 under **[My Details](https://mymobile.o2.co.uk/mydetails "MyO2")**
  * Your debit or credit card details, bank details and other payment information

**What you use your O2 products and services for**

Your call, text, surfing and billing records (for example) Or any other products from us you use, like our apps - this includes the date and time you use them, how long for, where you use them and how much it costs. We don't look at the content of your messages or listen to your calls (unless you are talking to one of our customer service advisors).

**Where you use our network**

So we can connect you to our network, we need to know your location when you make or receive phone calls, messages or use the internet. We call this network location, it finds you through phone masts nearby and only knows roughly where you are so that we can put calls through or connect you to the Internet.

Your smartphone might have also a Global Positioning System (GPS) location that is used by your phone and certain apps. It's more accurate than network location alone, because it uses satellites. We don't use your GPS location for calls, messages or internet access, generally. It's only if you're using some of our apps, like Priority Moments, that we might collect some of your GPS location information.

**What you do with your O2 account(s)**

This includes things like when and how much you top up and pay your bill or how often and why you access your account with us.

**How you use O2 Money**

For example: what you use O2 Money products and card services for. And what payments and transactions are going through at shops and with our partners.

Back to the top

### Where do we get your information?

We collect information mainly when you sign up with us, contact us and when you use our products and services.

For example when you::

  * Register as an O2 customer or take part in market research
  * Get in touch with us to ask something
  * Buy from us – whether it's in one of our shops, online, over the phone or somewhere else
  * Enter any promotions, competitions or prize draws through one of our services
  * Make changes to or close your O2 account
  * Go to our website, or the sites of any other companies in the Telefónica Group
  * Use any of our networks – mobile, wifi or other O2 products and services
  * Sign up for a service with us and we need to check with credit reference and fraud prevention agencies
  * Apply for a job with us online

We also collect information from other sources, including business directories and other commercially or publicly available sources.

Back to the top

### How we use your information

We use and analyse your information to keep in touch with you and to supply and improve our products and services. Sometimes we'll aggregate and anonymise this information so you won't be identified as an individual.

In particular this means using your information to:

  * Give you access to parts of the O2 website, like MyO2
  * Sort out a payment, put your order through our system or send you anything you order
  * Get in touch with you (like if we need to tell you about any problems with a service, or help you with any questions you have about our services or products)
  * Keep things secure and prevent crime and fraud
  * Look into any complaints or questions you may raise
  * Check whether you qualify for credit. This is so we can assess and decide on whether we can give you (and members of your household) credit, credit-related services, other similar facilities or insurance.
  * Trace and recover debts, manage credit, detect and prevent fraud and money laundering
  * Recover any money you might owe us
  * Assign your debt to permitted third parties. And look after any credit you might have

Or to:

  * Tell you if we've changed the way a service works. Or tell you about a new service that we think may interest you
  * Check what you're interested in, so we can offer (and develop) products and services you're actually interested in
  * Look at markets. Write reports. Do research and number crunching. And (if the law allows it) look at information about you (including the calls you make, your spending, what you use the internet for and where you are when you do it). As an individual or as a group
  * Send you information about our products and services (or those from chosen third parties we think you'd be interested in).By phone, post, email, text, picture message, online banner advertising, or other ways – unless you opt out
  * Tell you about products and services from other companies we think you'd be interested in, or let chosen third parties tell you directly about their products and services. You can opt out of messages like this too

Back to the top

### How we share your information

To run our business and provide you with our services, we may share your information with others.

This might mean sharing your information with:

  * Our partner companies or agencies and their sub-contractors or prospective partners who help us run our services, for example our [billing](http://www.ibm.com/uk/en "IBM") or [customer service centres](http://www.capita.co.uk/ "Capita")
  * Other companies in the Telefónica Group. This includes, [Telefonica Dynamic Insights](http://dynamicinsights.telefonica.com/479/about-us "Telefonica Dynamic Insights") and their respective partners, agents and sub-contractors
  * Insurance providers when you take out a policy through us
  * Offers we have your permission to send out to you from third parties, such as through [O2 More](http://www.o2more.co.uk/ "O2 More")
  * Products and services, including apps. For example, location information is used by apps like our [Priority Moments](http://www.o2priority.co.uk/moments "Priority Moments") . By agreeing and using them, you're giving us your consent to share your information with other companies who run these services
  * Credit reference and fraud prevention agencies
  * Other communications companies
  * New or prospective owners of Telefónica UK Limited

To comply with legal or regulatory obligations, we might share your information:

  * With any public authority or law enforcement agency (if they ask for it)
  * To comply with law or regulations. Or for possible legal proceedings
  * If you give us personal information that's wrong or we find out (or think) you're responsible for fraud
  * If one of our partners who are processing information for us are compelled to do so by law
  * If there's an emergency and we think you or other people are at risk.

Back to the top

### We keep hold of your information

There are certain reasons we have to keep hold of your information.

We keep information while you're our customer or after you've left us, but only as long as we need it. How long we keep it depends very much on the type of information and purpose. For example, we might need to sort out disagreements, stop fraud and abuse, prove that you had an account with us or follow our legal obligations. Or if the police needs it as evidence. We may also keep information about how you use our products or services.

Back to the top

### Want to check and update your information?

It's your information. Just ask if you want a copy.

**Your personal information**

Go to o2.co.uk and [sign in](https://accounts.o2.co.uk/signin "sign in to My O2") to My O2'(link to: https://accounts.o2.co.uk/signin) to look at your personal information. You can change how we get in touch with you – and your account details – whenever you like.

**Marketing communications**

If you don't want us or our partner companies to send you relevant offers or marketing information, you can opt out anytime via your PC in **My O2** , by clicking on the **My Choices** link in the My Mobile section. These changes can only be made using your PC - you won't be able to see this option if you are accessing My O2 via the app or the mobile website on your phone.

**Your location**

Network location uses our network to find your phone so we can connect your call. If you don't want us to share your network location for some or all of your services, call us on 1300. It's free from your O2 mobile. 

GPS location is different network location. We don't control it, so there's no need to call 1300. GPS is based on satellites and is set up on the mobile phone itself. Look at your phone's settings to configure it.

Please remember, if you choose not to share your location you might not be able to use certain services that need to know where you are in order to work.

**Find out more about your information**

If you want, we can send you the information we have about you. There are a couple of ways to do this and some requests have to be in writing because of legal requirements. Details on how to do this [can be found here](http://www.o2.co.uk/help/everything-else/how-to-get-a-copy-of-the-information-we-store-about-you#qs).

Back to the top

### Important things to know

**The lowdown on cookies**

Like other sites, we use cookies. A cookie is like a tag that some sites put on your computer or phone when you visit them so they can recognise you next time. Find out more [here.](http://www.o2.co.uk/cookie-policy "Cookie policy")

**Communicating over the internet**

Any emails or other communications you send over the internet aren't safe unless they've been encrypted. They might go through a few countries before they get to your friend who lives around the corner. That's the nature of the internet.

If someone gets into your emails without your permission, or your personal information is shared publicly, we can't accept responsibility .It's out of our control.

**Pages on o2.co.uk and other companies' sites**

On our website there are pages that are branded with both the O2 name and logo, as well as other companies' names and logos. We, and other companies working with us, look after these pages.

This privacy policy doesn't apply to other companies' sites that you get to through our website. So make sure you've read a company's privacy policy before putting your personal information on their site.

**Companies outside the European Economic Area (EEA)**

We might give your information to other companies based outside the EEA.Like many companies, we may use cloud services from a supplier outside the EEA.

And finally, please note that if you're signing up for our products and services there might be extra terms and conditions to look at.

Back to the top
